BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.541089: California Metal Trades Association, Warehouse Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 860, 1967- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.551743: California Bakery Employers Association and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 24, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Code no.560019: Chicago Packers and Sausage Manufacturers and Meat and Highway Drivers, Dockmen, Helpers, and Misc. Truck Terminal Employees, Local 710, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Code no.570814: Union Oil Company and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 1-128, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - Code no.550688: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 556, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 556, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 12/18/1964 and expires on 03/31/1967. Covers 525 workers in California.
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
  - Code no.550849: Self-Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, 1964- 1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Self-Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 10/04/1964 and expires on 10/07/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Cook County, IL.
    - Item 2: Self-Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 10/08/1967 and expires on 10/03/1970. Covers 1430 workers in Cook County, IL.
  - Code no.550850: Self-Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320-571, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320-571, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 320, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 10/08/1967 and expires on 10/03/1970. Covers 1200 workers in Cook County, IL.
  - Code no.550851: Self-Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 547, 1964- 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 547, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 2: Service Meat Markets, Chicago and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 547, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 10/08/1967 and expires on 10/03/1970. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Cook County, IL.
  - Code no.551740: Furr's, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1564, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Foodway and others, and Retail Clerks Union Local 1564, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 10/20/1967 and expires on 10/20/1970. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New Mexico.
    - Item 2: Furr's, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1564, 1965-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 07/15/1965 and expires on 07/15/1966. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New Mexico.
  - Code no.561052: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Meat Cutters District Union 427, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Meat Cutters District Union 427, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 09/02/1968 and expires on 09/05/1971. Covers 500 workers in Cleveland, OH.
    - Item 2: The Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, District Union 427, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 09/04/1965 and expires on 09/08/1968. Covers 600 workers in Cleveland, OH.
  - Code no.570218: Chicago Car Dealers and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Chicago Car Dealers and International Association of Machinists & Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1965-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1965 and expires on 07/01/1967. Covers 415 workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Code no.570571: Giant, of Baltimore Food Employers Labor Relations Association and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 692, 1967- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Giant Food Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 692, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 01/22/1967 and expires on 07/19/1969. Covers 725 workers in Baltimore, MD.
  - Code no.580004: Chain and Independent Food Stores, Albuquerque, NM and Retail Clerks Union Local 1564, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Code no.580178: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 2, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 2, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 11/12/1967 and expires on 02/14/1970. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New England.
- Series IX: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.540912: Scruggs-Vandervoort-Barney, Inc. (and others) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 709, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes Stix, Baer, and Fuller Co.; Famous-Barr Co.; Associated Retailers Suburban Delivery Co.
- Series X: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.560614: Vacuum Cooler Agreement, California and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 890, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Code no.561422: Motor Transport Labor Relations, Inc. and Garage Parking and Service Station Employees Union, Local 596, IBT, 1966- 1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Code no.570640: Phillips Pipe Line Company and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 109, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Code no.590097: Mobil Oil Corporation and Socony Mobil Boatmen's Union, Western River Towboats, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Series XI: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.551191: Continental Forwarding Service, Inc. and Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, Local 688, IBT, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Code no.560652: Warehouse Employers and International Longshoremen's Association and Marine Terminal and Warehousemen's Locals 783, 976-4, 1478-2, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Code no.571058: Ravenna Arsenal, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4581, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Series XII: Industry Code #54, Realt Estate and Rental and Leasing
  - Code no.560620: Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. - CBS Records Division and United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 237, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Code no.570040: Indiana Bell Telephone Company, Inc. and Communications Workers of America, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Code no.570096: Tacoma Broadcasters, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 77, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Code no.590100: Pacific Telephone and Communications Workers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Series XIII: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
  - Code no.590063: Community Memorial Hospital Association and Retail Clerks International Assoc., Local 1116, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)